EPRIS BURNETT

WEB DEVELOPER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

MOBILE

EMAIL 248.730.8645 eharrisburnett@gmail.com **LOCATION**

Cornelius, NC

ESDHB0906.GITHUB.IO | LINKEDIN.COM/IN/EPRISHB

Web developer for 4 years; graphic designer for over 10 years. Primary tech stack is MERN. Currently diving into LAMP stack to build custom WordPress themes and plugins. Customers are first as happy and well-informed customers drive results. Agile and goal-oriented worker believing in beating deadlines, not meeting them.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BROOKS EQUIPMENT / BHC ISS

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT Web Developer & Graphic Designer Charlotte, NC Feb 2019

- Collaborated with IT in building two eCommerce sites and a service site from the ground up.
- Implement Google Marketing Platform. (Analytics, Tag Manager) and Google Search Console into eCommerce sites for eCommerce tracking and SEO purposes.
- Perform web maintenance on 7 company sites including making older sites accessible, mobilefriendly, optimized for search engines - and redeveloping the site when UI/UX needs to be updated.
- Increased web traffic by 6 7% by implementing fundamental SEO strategy alongside the marketing team.
- Integrate HubSpot into sites for automated email, marketing processes, and form capturing
- Assist graphic designers with heavy workloads by creating web banners, optimizing images for web, and developing catalogs and deliverables to keep customers informed on the latest products and industry standards

BOY SCOUTS OF AMERICA

ADVERTISING

Graphic Designer Charlotte, NC Aug 2018

- Maintained design consistency in sales sheets
- Created ads for Scout Shops promotional events
- Developed banners and flyers for kits

BRADLEY CO.

PROMOTIONAL MERCHANDISING Graphic Designer Southfield, MI May 2017 - 2018

- Managed up to 20+ projects simultaneously, including rush orders, with deadlines of 24 hours or less
- Created presentations for web store advertisement banners for various clients
- Curated email blasts for PPG Paint yearly calendars via MailChimp and Illustrator

APPLET SOCIAL

WEB & APP DEVELOPMENT Project Manager Detroit, MI Sep 2014 - 2018

- Managed multiple projects and organized team communication via Podio project management system
- Utilized HTML/CSS in conjunction with ShoutEm to produce apps

CONTINENTAL SERVICES

DINING & CATERING

Graphic Designer Troy, MI Sep 2012 - 2014

- Developed and managed branding across 7 venues
- Collaborated with cafe managers and web designer to ensure proper promotion of products and sales increase
- Successfully launched digital menu boards in over 5 cafe locations including General Motors and Mercedes Benz Financial Center

SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, React

Web: HTML/CSS, Responsive Web Design,

Accessibility

Framework/Libraries: Bootstrap, Material UI, Framer, React Hooks Forms, Styled Components Adobe Creative Cloud: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, XD, Dreamweaver, After Effects,

Acrobat, Lightroom

CMS/CRM: WordPress, HubSpot,

OS: Windows, Linux, Mac

PROJECTS

Memory Game (JavaScript)
Feed Reader Testing (Jasmine)
My Reads (React)
Neighborhood Map (React)

EDUCATION

2018 - 2018

BACHELORS OF ART

GRAPHIC DESIGN
Southern New Hampshire University
Manchester, NH

2018

NANODEGREE

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPMENT Udacity
Online